[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these pairs, movie -- its director is wrong?", "correct_answer": "Sleepy Hollow (1999) - Francis Ford Coppola", "incorrect_answers": ["Hellraiser (1987) - Clive Barker", "Armageddon (1998) - Michael Bay", "Rose Red (2002) - Craig R. Baxley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first Soviet nuclear ballistic submarine was called K-(this number).", "correct_answer": "19", "incorrect_answers": ["18", "17", "21"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the Clone Commander of the 501st legion in the Star Wars movies?", "correct_answer": "Cody", "incorrect_answers": ["Joe", "Bob", "Collin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Orange Pekoe is a type of what?", "correct_answer": "Tea", "incorrect_answers": ["Tropical Fish", "Gemstone", "Wildflower"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Pirates of the Caribbean: At Worlds End, Will stabbed the heart of Davy Jones with his fathers knife.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Judd Apatow is the producer of the 2008 comedy Forgetting Sarrah Marshall. Which of the actors, who star in it, is also the writer of the movie?", "correct_answer": "Jason Segel", "incorrect_answers": ["Mila Kunis", "Jonah Hill", "Russell Brand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sesame is an annual plant , whose closest relatives originated in which continent?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "Europe", "Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is untrue?", "correct_answer": "When a gorilla is angry it shows its teeth.", "incorrect_answers": ["Mosquitoes have teeth.", "The Statue of Libertys teeth are 3 feet wide.", "Lemon sharks  grow new teeth every two weeks."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Located in the upper anterior portion of the chest cavity, the thymus is an organ belonging to which system of the human body?", "correct_answer": "Lymphatic System", "incorrect_answers": ["Endocrine system", "Integumentary system", "Nervous system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film industry, the term 2:3 pulldown refers to what?", "correct_answer": "The conversion of film to video", "incorrect_answers": ["The optimal difference of intensities between the key and the fill in high key lighting", "The amount of delay within in a recorded scene", "The order of a shot list"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Some sources claim the youngest pope was Benedict IX (1032 A.D.), elected at this age.", "correct_answer": "12", "incorrect_answers": ["21", "9", "16"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is regarded as the first internationally recognized celebrity chef?", "correct_answer": "Marie-Antoine Car\u00eame", "incorrect_answers": ["Wolfgang Puck", "Jeff Smith", "Paul Bocuse"]}]